The court order the rigorous given me mom City Guest 2 days. November 4th, 2020 5th,
but again, but on the given personal appearances, have 9, 3, 3, A, Klein's List.
Most two proof.
Section E, step 5.
4, 5, Jews.
High, double.
High, per person.
5, 3, B, F, and the over 21st, regular meeting.
Most two proof.
Second, E, step 5.
5, Jews.
High, double.
High, per person.
3, C, minutes.
On cover 28, 20, 20, 5, ready to be.
Motion to approve.
Second.
5, double.
High, Jews.
10, E, step 5.
High, per person.
5, D, 23, D, 246.
All days get over.
Motion to approve.
Second.
E, step 5.
5, Jews.
High, double.
High, per person.
3, E, 20, 26, meetings.
Good.
Second.
Double.
High.
Farms.
High, Jews.
E, step 5.
High, per person.
3, F.
Dominic Gordon is 20, 25, that's 0, 8, charter.
2.
Articles.
6.
Section 2.
1, 41.
3, 2, 1, 46.
This is just a, there was a scrubbinger's error in that four nominations that the publisher caught.
And we probably could have just had the mayor sign off on it, but from an abundance of caution,
I'd rather have the council approve.
It's a change in its five to six.
Can I make left one approve?
Second.
5.
Double.
High.
6.
Or it's 2025, that's 11.
A mini chapter 16.
Section 16.
That's six.
To encoder that new fees, get over the sports and write department for writing, for conflicting provisions,
for building all conflicting ordinances, and establishing an effective date.
So we were last week in the more session we brought to you guys, we had a piece of visual.
We wanted to update this as well.
We've got lots of other questions.
Some areas in the course side, there's butter on it.
So we've got an investment with the ability to do rent.
I'll stop for a video.
I'll also have a piece scheduled.
I'm burning up this, the flexibility, yeah, so we've been kind of handcuffed and looking at what kind of business
I've got a lot to do with this.
Part two, we have three of them out there, so we're going to use the place of the product and offer.
We've got one over at Brian's.
Do you have something to say?
I don't know, there's a part that I don't see in the club, man.
Can you please move in?
Yeah, look through it today.
I think it's a good idea.
I think we've got to recoup some of the bodies that we're spending for.
Staffing them out.
At the bottom of the piece, we've got four of the sports companies.
We've used the leaves that these are facilities.
They're basically used for free.
And they're not getting a little bit of a change.
We've got this.
With this and the five dollars per year to play.
We're just playing.
As of right now, in 2020, six.
The start of the session.
Do you see in the near future of us taking over the soccer?
They're both for strong right now.
I've got it.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
So, please.
For the time, Joe's time, E-CIP, Parker.
Hi.
Thank you.
3, 8, or it's 25, that's 12, and many chapter 16, 16, that's five,
that's the part of the recreation piece.
Get it off.
So, yeah, I'm just going to be back off with, you know,
trying to talk about, we had a lot of these fees that we had
to complete.
Okay.
And that's, you know, we're just kind of locked in on certain prices.
The students beability to enjoy their life.
And you have to be aware of everything.
And you have to say, we got in a criteria.
We'll just do a little bit of a case, okay?
Places.
Yeah.
I think it will be a bit different.
You can motion the broom.
Second.
Parker.
Aye.
For the time.
I'm hiring Andrew Donnie, as an alternate municipal court judge.
This came up.
Judge, I want to call him Chuck, it's not just Chuck.
If he brought it up that there was a, the case didn't make, but there was almost a case where his wife would have been a witness, and he would not have been able to adjudicate that.
So we discussed the need for an alternate judge, which would occur probably three to four times a year.
Her, our organist, Andrew Downey, if he is hired, has agreed that he would accept a hundred and fifty dollars per appearance to do that, just to stand in for Chuck when needed, and that would come out of Legels budget.
Motion to approve.
Hi.
Dennis, have you said?
3J.
This is the same memorandum to understand with the adult Honey Art.
We're in the library.
Library.
I blanked out what made you go so much for a minute.
Yeah, it's for the library, and if you look on the, in your packet it shows you what areas they're going to paint there, and that's painting over those crying.
That's one that's going to have the buffalo that you saw on the packet. That pretty much is going to look just like the island.
I make a motion to approach the brain over.
A second.
Two words. Five.
Two.
One.
Hi.
Is that part of the?
Three case, mission.
That way, we're pulled of loop to host the summer mirrors.
Council of Oklahoma in 16th to 19th, 206.
So that's me, but we want some of it in the boat.
I was asked by Mayor Parker to get together in the facts and figures for a proposed mayor's conference.
That week, that's the 16th through the 19th and 2026.
I believe in your packet, you have what came from the league in terms of who's responsible for what in terms of catering venue,
who's paying for what whether it's a participant or whether it's a city.
So before we submit the proposal, I wanted to share with you the cost that would be agreed by the city.
Those are estimated catering costs, who knows where we'll be in a year.
We could be cheaper. We could be higher.
I think that there are some other avenues we could also take to reduce that cost a little bit also.
Before we ever submit the proposal and then we'd do by December 19th and then we wouldn't know anything until January.
So this is just approval.
We may not be put.
I won't bring about a hundred mayor's or also state to your community in June.
16th to the 19th.
It's also the same league that eight men is in terms.
Also.
So you'll have to find money in the budget for it.
I'm just saying, because you will have to admit it.
The whole word you vote, which is you, and you cannot spend money that you're not.
Well, we're just given her the okay to submit it.
But if we're chosen.
And we want to know that.
Oh, it's too approve. I have questions. Oh, is that okay if we are approved they will just like probably go to all the apartments and just have them cut their budget
Surprise
I don't know it's hard to say because we mean it's like we don't spend a lot then it goes fast, you know
Quick, yeah, I mean that could be a possibility
So we'll know and Jane, well, we know you said
So if we were to occur well, I guess that would be us doing this right now
We may not be accepted. I heard something at some point, but we would know and Jane
We'll be able to come back and say
I mean we'll make anything weird. That's what we do is in it. Yeah
I'm just love that
But I will say that the first time Tyler and I'm having a trend that was 25,000
Yeah, and Tyler about how to strip but right off the red did a dump on the street
Anyway, we get to look good team. So who knows to trend that she's like not them the 12 something
So
Transportation was one of the big ones that we ran for rent some buses to make people around so I've got to hold a deal about them
So good mom's goals
Then we'll ask you they're more or less this didn't move people around that way
We're not rent buses that same money, but so she got down below 12, but around she's not around
I'll just go to ask and tell them to drive on
I'm hoping it's expired
Hi
We've got two of them, get you now
Really?
I didn't say it worked. I can find the money, they've played six and things
So we just need to make a recommendation to
for example, for member of the fire 11728.
Question 2.
Second.
But we're seeing nomination.
We want Colby out into the final commission of this year's bureau.
For term groups, fire 1121 to 28.
Second.
So I get
I
B
Of
Team
B
For I, nomination to appoint Lee and Walker to the Board of Justice,
how's the authority,
my opinion?
Question 2?
Question 2.
By your point,
sorry for your point,
please go ahead and point.
Question 2.
Be seated.
All right.
Start,
sorry.
I'm from Howard K.
No, madam.
I was in the area in the morning.
I was in the public area.
We don't get to that.
I'm not going to need you.
I'm going to if I'm going to do it.
Thank you.
VON.
All right.
Is it James?
I'm James.
You know?
I wasn't going to do it.
James?
We're standing there.
We will get in the middle of this.
Was a student that said I'd go get the voter.
You know?
We'll go there.
I would love to see you.
Okay.
We'll be back.
I'd like to.
Thank you.
The set of the mayor council and unity announced, but yeah, I want to apologize for
missing last week's meeting.
I didn't realize we had a meeting and it was all my fault, so please forgive me.
Oh, you wasn't here?
Great turn out for Booge Hall Hall and I think it was a number of about 3,000 people, we're
downtown.
All right.
That's really cool.
So there was a long line, there was a lot of people, you know what, two of those two, the team
that took that on, because there was like, it's not much right needed to be community.
It really is.
And I know it's kind of got passed to us, the handle and I'm glad we did, because a lot of families
counted on it.
And a lot of, a lot of kids lost my own faces.
And I know my, we only took mine through one side, because the line was long, and that
we were only eight, but they're about to be full.
That's safe place for me.
Yeah, that's safe place.
So my company gave away 1,500 boxes in an hour and a half.
That's awesome.
It was good stuff.
I appreciate everybody that had something to do with that.
I know I saw Chris.
Chris was nice guy.
Chris stuff was fire fires.
It's really good stuff.
Chris, that was a place for Ellie.
But I appreciate all of you.
But I appreciate everybody's efforts, because I know there's a lot for you guys.
So we couldn't do the things we do without all of this.
So we appreciate each other very much.
Of course, we got holidays coming up.
I'll say, you guys are already hanging.
Separations.
Yes, all of that on the way over.
Awesome.
I love this time of year.
So I appreciate you guys doing that.
I know you have a lot of stuff you'd rather be doing.
But it really makes downbound at five.
So I appreciate you guys as efforts.
So he must.
Then the great city manager.
There's a couple of things.
We have the annual gal, so if you'd like to go, let me know if people have let me know if they want to go or not.
Also, we have the kids giving, coming up, so I send an email on that, so if you'd like to go, let us know when we want to make sure you have it.
See at the table announcement, of course, the holiday market, number 14th and 15th,
they're doing a canned food drive during the holiday market,
it dropped off non-perishables at the CVB office.
The next thing is kind of a cool announcement that the Chief just came and told me today and I got an email.
So I know him and Glenn that worked on, we got a grant for cameras, and they can get a new seat.
The key cameras?
So I've asked the Chief to work with our local partners, such as the Trips, such as other agencies, to help us like fun, you know, the coming year.
So we got the grant to get the cameras, but we're upset to pay every year to keep them.
So to help us.
That's awesome.
The Chief went to talk about this a lot, so I was very excited to this big time to get those.
But I had a question on, if you know the answer to this or not, if you don't, it's okay.
Does this have any spot cameras? Does that help our community members with their, um, homeowners interest?
But all?
They could probably use that to report that you have.
Not necessarily homeowners, but to reduce crashes.
It's not that the crashes.
You can throw away this and it's not that.
So they could probably use that.
We could do it.
That's something that may help homeowners.
Okay.
Cool.
And, uh, I know, correct me from wrong, but not too long ago, the qualification has some block cameras.
They have wind outside some block cameras.
And these will all work together.
But we will have access across the nation.
Okay.
And so, if we not get a stolen car in Miami that would pick that block one of those cameras,
it's going to be like ball bar somewhere, but we're not at all of this.
So it says it can't do it.
It team the last place is stolen.
And they got stolen bar.
So, uh, then, then, that here, we got 10.
Yes.
So we got 10 cameras.
So they built place in the major intersection of downtown.
In the downtown.
And I'm in that town.
So, maybe, maybe big.
How soon or before does it get installed?
Well, we had to go up a bit.
We had to go up a bit.
And we got to go up a bit.
We got to go up a bit.
Okay.
So, the six thing means.
So, I started getting installed.
Yeah.
We have to do a plan meeting.
We're going to put him in the house.
We'll just see what the clock on has in place.
So, he'll play up the back as well.
So, I'm not going to be serious at all.
I'm not going to be serious at all.
I'm going to be serious at all.
So, um, the camera's in.
up there just for reading plates or if there's a crime at a business can we go back and look
those cameras and see what cards were coming by and so if we have a big group of restrictions,
any type of restriction, even a light truck, we can search every camera that came for a
light truck or we can go and look at certain cameras, let's say something happened to me and
said we got a camera down at CBOC and CBOC and CBOC and CBOC and CBOC and CBOC and went through
areas so it maintains all those tags that go through for 30 days and for us it'd be
big too because a lot of the crime that we've seen kind of comes from a town that
come in and there's even or whatever then go back up down to that would be a cool
have you going in and out and out of town do you hear where how to distract no sex
and then there are even access groups, yes, obviously for our customers, and it's like a 30
symptom, no or there is $3,000 per camera per year plus it's around $5,000,000, just a
less than six to two for the price that created what they call the policy consortium, they are
looking at it, I have to apply for it and then the nice thing is that I apply for next year I think
such a thing, got a nice feeling for those cameras, I want to
And then even find more location, do you like to put them at visualize something big, are you
going to miss everything down down in there emotion, sir.
Okay.
or D.